Hello and welcome to Agency Access. My
name is Kevin, founder and I'm going to
guide you through the platform in a few
quick minutes. So once you're under the
platform, the first thing you want to do
is to connect your account to agency
access. Otherwise, you can't request
access to any other accounts obviously.
So in order to do that, you go on the
left hand side, you go to accounts and
you choose the one uh you want to link
with. uh in my example in the case um
I'm a PPC expert and I want access to
their analytics for tracking purposes
their tech manager and their Google ads
obviously. So um obviously those are all
Google services we have meta now and
we're working on a lot of other services
as well. So in order to do that we go to
uh link and you'll select your Google
account. Click continue.
And it takes a few seconds to link your
account.
Okay, we're linked. Um, and we can send
a link right away. But before I want to
send a link, I want to yeah, be sure
that it looks like my agency look like
it coming from my agency and it ensures
the like the professionality. So, uh, in
order to do so, we go to branding. I
want to make it look like my own agency.
So, my agency color is red. Um, and you
can choose a dark mode or like a white
mode. I like the white. And uh, choose
your name,
agency name. I can add my own logo. I
can add it to my own subdomain. Um, and
you can like see how it's going to look
here. So, I made a typo.
Um, and once you're happy with it, you
can just save changes. You get a success
message. And now you're ready to send a
request. So to do so, you go back to the
dashboard. You're going to create a link
to a new client. The client's going to
uh name is going to be
new client
from new company
newest.com. It doesn't really matter.
And we're going to use XXL nutrition
nutrition
as example. Uh you have to choose if
it's going to be a client. So you can
request admin access. Uh if it's going
to be prospect, you only be able to
request uh read only access uh to Google
Messa etc etc. So it's going to be
client. I'm going to create my new link.
Um as said earlier I want access to ads
analytics and tag manager. Uh I'll just
admin
continue. This is what the link is going
to look like. Um, it's based off your
branding set settings. And if you're not
happy, you can change it right here or
go back to branding. Um, it looks fine
to me. So, we're going to continue. And
you can add a custom thank you message
or you can redirect after uh they're
done through your custom thank you page,
for example. Um, it's not relevant to
me, so I'm just going to continue. And
this is uh the preview of the send. Um I
can include um let agency access send an
email to your client with hey um um this
agency request access to your account um
you want to guarant uh obviously you can
just uncheck and send it yourself uh
even through like WhatsApp or something
if you prefer that.
Once you're ready send it
takes a few seconds
and the link is created. You'll see it
here. It says pending because they
haven't accepted it yet. Once they
connect any of the services, it will um
yeah, the light indicator will turn
green real time. And once all are done,
it will be granted. Um good thing to
know, you can send a reminder, for
example, if they haven't replied or
granted access to all the services, you
could do so once every two hours, I
believe. Um, if you want to send it to
multiple people, you can CC another
person with their name and email and
we'll send the mail notification. Um,
that's optional. You can send it to
someone else as well. Or you can uh edit
the message. So if you say okay, I also
want access to their search console for
example as an owner. I can do so update
it. It will update in real time. So
that's really cool. Um, I can copy the
link here and I can also
uh good to know. If you need us, please
go to the chat widget on the right or
click on support, it will open and we'll
be here to help you. Um, also good to
know if you go to referrals um and you
can um create a referral account you can
get up to uh 20%
uh on the people you refer on their
subscription. So if you refer a few
people um yeah it can be interesting for
you as well. Again thank you for
choosing Agency Access and we hope the
platform is useful for you and if you
need us you know where to find us. Thank
you.